So welcome ladies.
This is very much like George's call so I'm not I'm not taking any like lim
elight here.
She always does this call and always plans it every year and it's like a really
popular
call.
We all enjoy doing like setting our goals and feeling motivated at the start of
the year.
And so I'll hand over to you, shall I do and just let me know if you want me to
chip in.
Thank you.
Yeah, you can chip in whenever you like or not.
It's entirely up to you and but thank you for the introduction, a little bit of
pressure
now.
Okay, then.
So let's get started, shall we?
Also, one of the girls has just messaged me to say that she's a full name is
shown on
the screen just to let you know and it's not because the full names that I show
and wasn't
knew that message.
So don't worry.
And okay, let's get started.
Okay, then, so hello 2024 and speaking of the moon, we're going to do some
exercises
involved in the moon today.
So as it's the new year, it's the perfect time to set our intentions and to
leave anything
that is not serving us behind in 2023 and also celebrate what we left behind
last year.
Okay, so let us ourselves.
What did I let go of last year that like really saved a purpose in my life.
So is there anything that was holding us back last year that we left and like
made a difference
in our life?
We can also ask ourselves, what do I need to let go of now?
So is there anything still that I'm holding on to that's not serving me that I
need to
let go of before moving into the new year?
And finally, what limiting belief about myself do I need to leave behind?
So I'm sure that we all have something that we tell ourselves that's not so
positive or
something that we need to change a way that we view ourselves because I feel
like the way
that we view ourselves ultimately defines how we live our lives, you know what
I mean?
If we believe that we're worthy and we're destined for great things and we
deserve a
beautiful, happy life and that will happen because we'll make sure we give
ourselves
that.
But if we don't feel too good about ourselves and I feel like we're just going
to just
be making decisions or choices that aren't so great and before I let you get
started
with that, I'll just explain a little bit about the current moon phase.
So right now it's the waning, present moon and this is a period to fully let go
.
So it's perfectly with this exercise.
So it's a good time to rest and prepare for the new cycle ahead as well.
So once we've let go of what we need to let go of tonight, we can have a really
beautiful
rest, no one, we've let go of all of that negative energy or you know those
emotions
that we don't need to hold on to.
And this moon phase is also best for surrendering to the natural flow of life,
resting and rejuvenating
your energy.
This sounds really good to me at the minute because I feel like this is what I
need.
So yeah, let's do these free questions please girls on our pens and paper.
And then if anyone would like to share at the end, we can.
We've had a couple of people just join a little bit late.
So just to let you know, George has just chatted through this first slide.
So if you want to have a little read through, we're just answering the
questions on this
slide.
We're just writing them down and then we'll come back to chat about them.
Thank you.
A lot.
A lot of people have been there for a long time and they're really excited to
see
us.
I'm not sure.
I can't believe we're going to take that.
And that's a lot of people.
I'm not sure.
I'm sure that's a lot of people.
But I'm sure that's a lot of people who are going to need to be able to answer
questions
about what we're going to do.
And I'm sure that's a lot of people who are going to do this.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
How is everyone getting on?
Are you almost finished or do you need a bit more time?
Yeah, you're done.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
I give it another minute or two just to make sure everyone is finished.
Or would anybody like to share their one of their answers or all of their
answers?
Well, people are finishing off.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
I would share, okay.
Yeah, I was thinking about last year, because we did this a similar exercise
last year.
And I think it's so nice to like acknowledge what we put last year and what we
thought about.
Because it wasn't until you did this that I thought about what I'd put last
year.
And what I put last year was, what I wanted to let go of was negative body
image.
Not all the time, but just body perfectionism.
I just wanted to be a peak fitness all the time.
I feel like I've done that a lot.
I've even been to parties where I'm not worn very much when I'm on my period or
not feeling at my best.
I've definitely come a long way with that, so it's a nice certain knowledge.
And also like a bad money story, like I always was like really anxious about
money.
And even when I even want to start to have a little bit of money, I was anxious
about that.
So I was like, well, I'm going to lose it.
So yeah, and I've really come a long way without now as well.
And so yeah, it was really nice to think about last year, what I said last year
and how much difference has been.
That's good. Thank you for sharing. That's nice to hear.
Because yeah, it's like from somebody else's opinion, looking at you.
It's crazy to think you would ever have a negative body image, you know what I
mean?
But of course, I understand how it is because I'm the same sometimes, you know.
But yeah, I'm glad that you've come a long way with that.
And yeah, it's nice that you can look back on it and see that you've let it go.
Or at least you're working to let it go, you know, of course, like.
I still think like I was also looking back at my one last year and I was
thinking to myself, maybe like.
Not throughout the whole year, or maybe not all the time, like, you know, I've
let it go, but.
I have as much as possible, you know, but of course, we're still human and
those feelings can creep back in.
But it's just a case of like switching online sets and like.
Yeah, so yes, thank you for sharing, dear.
Was anybody else like to share before we move on?
I like to share.
Yeah, go ahead.
Something I let go off was my fear of public speaking.
I still have a very like, like anxiety.
For centing at work or whatnot.
So I really had to basically fake it until I made it and it worked.
Amazing.
Oh, it's nice to hear.
Yeah, thank you for sharing and speaking on here now shows that you are like.
Working even more to like letting go of that because obviously you're speaking
in front of people here.
So thank you for sharing that Rebecca.
Okay, then we'll move on then, shall we, Gillies?
Okay.
Now that we have let go of what is no longer seven hours, let's take a look at
what we want to achieve this year.
And to your mind.
And some snazzy things on this, aren't you?
What was that?
Snazzy things on this PowerPoint.
Okay, so make a list of absolutely everything that you want to achieve this
year.
Big or small, it doesn't matter.
Just write it down.
For example, it could be something as big as I want to make it a positive on a
house, or it could be something just as small as you want to end every shower
with a cold rinse, or you want to teach your dog how to sit or even take the
bins out or whatever.
Literally could don't think don't just think you have to think of like the big
goals that are going to take a lot of time and effort. Just think of everything
.
So we'll take five minutes and we'll just write down all of the goals that we
hope to achieve this year.
Sorry, can you just press next on the next one, please? Well, just to check if
there's anything I need to now that's fine. Okay. Thank you.
Now that's fine. Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Right girls with about halfway through just a couple more minutes just think,
and of all the things you'd like to achieve.
Thank you.
Okay girls, we'll move on now, but if you haven't finished, and there's more
that you need to add, you can always go back at the end and just go through all
of the stuff that you didn't complete and add it in at the end.
But we'll move on to the next bit now.
So now that we have this list, we would like to organise it, and we can do this
by writing one, two or three next to the goals, write a one next to the goals
that can be achieved quite easily with little to no effort.
So, for example, if you're one of your goals was to take the bins out, for
example, I know, like I said, that's not really like a huge on, but I wanted
everything on there. You can just write a one next to that because that can be
done, you know, straight away.
Or if it needs a little bit more effort and time and energy, write a two next
to it, and then write a three next to the goals that will take a lot of work.
So obviously the ones that are going to take maybe most of the year.
So we can do this now.
Thank you.
I love that Sammy, that's him. A good way of doing it.
Oh, I said I like that Sammy, because Sammy wrote in the chat that she writes
it out as if like, she's achieved like it's a spell, you know what I mean, like
, obviously all words are very important what we're saying.
So yeah, so she writes it out as if like she's already done it, kind of thing,
like she's achieved it already.
Okay, then we can move on to the next thing if that's okay well.
If this list as it is coming back one more sorry, sorry, thank you.
And we're just going to leave this list as it is and we'll come back to it
later, but before we move on would anybody like to share any goals that they
have for this year.
I will start, and maybe then I'll inspire some people to share as well.
Okay, so some of my goals are to by land in Thailand and start building some
homes there.
I would like to be able to do this full splits and the pancake something I've
been working towards for years but I've not got there yet and I feel like it's
not being a priority and that's why I've not got there but it will be this year
.
Another goal which I probably shouldn't share but I will, it's just become like
a little bit more mentally like stable because I feel like recently I've
honestly just been a bit everywhere.
So a goal of mine at the moment is to just start therapy and just become a
little bit more.
Yeah, just more stable and more like I don't know if the way to stable I think
it's just more just more at peace in my own mind and be kind to to myself as a
goal and to make better decisions that another goal.
So there's some of my goals for this year.
Was anybody else like to share.
No, okay we can move on.
Do you want me to share.
Yeah.
Okay, so I've got travel more, which I did pretty well with last year so just
one of the things is take both my kids away abroad because last year only took
one away abroad.
Because he's older and the other one we just did holidays in the UK so just
take them both abroad this year.
Another one is to have some new generous regular clients because some of the
ones I've had.
I just you know like after a couple of years it kind of gets a bit stale one a
bit.
Some of them can like sort of go off the radar a little bit so have a sort of
you know really at home and I'm getting some new really generous regular
clients, at least two with a better daytime routine.
I'm a balanced home life and taking a bit of time to spend with my partner
actually having fun together because we get very stuck in that world of like
mum and dad and routine and stuff like that so I think that's quite important.
And to go to more raves. I would definitely want to go to a few more raves this
year because I always have like a bit of a limiting belief that I'm a bit too
old and that's just not true.
I'm getting shape a little bit more because my boobs done this year.
And my big goal is to have a campervan.
Oh, amazing. Thank you for sharing Sammy.
And I love how we've listened to all Sammy's goals come true in the past so for
like yeah I'm excited for all those come true to you as well.
Definitely.
Amazing, but anybody else like to share.
I can share a few. So similar to you G, I put like mental stuff so I put there.
Hold on, which is not scary.
So sometimes I feel like I hang on to like past stuff and I feel a bit like a
victim to it so move past those feelings and then like learning to like check
in with myself and achieve like stillness and awareness.
Especially when I'm in environments where I'm overstimulated and like short
circuiting and not like feeling my feelings. So that's one.
I want to thrive in a physical and an autistic hobby.
So yeah, like not so much like the gym, but more like a craft or something like
that.
So one of my body was my mind.
I want to go on two holidays this year. You want us to go to Mexico.
And I want to have a better relationship with my parents.
And I want to have like a daily therapeutic practices like part of my daily
life like in my routine.
Yeah.
That's so amazing. Thank you for sharing.
No, I love it. Yeah.
Thank you dear.
Okay, we'll move on to the next slide then please well.
It made me tear up Jess.
Okay then so bear with me on this one I know my sounds a bit more birds but I
feel like it's going to be a good one.
I know in death bed manifesto, which actually came from rel she listened to
something recently on the radio and it inspired us to do this one.
And before we move on Sophie just wrote about her goal so I'll just read it out
.
So she's wrote my big goal is to have a healthy baby.
Then I'd like to just then I'd like to just get through the happily with lots
of fun and two little ones are that so sweet.
Sophie's due very soon and just over a month's time so in so yeah how exciting.
Okay then so I'll get back to the death bed manifesto and okay so we've looked
at what we've what we want to achieve.
Now let's think about the meaning in our lives.
Okay so let's imagine what on our death bed again please bear with me on this
one.
What are the three things you hope you will have achieved during your life.
For example, made a difference to people had time to do the things I enjoy
spent less time worrying about things that were out of my control.
So instead of maybe thinking about goals like you know by the car or you know
by a house or whatever.
I think like these ones are more like more like emotional girls you know what I
mean more ones that are like.
Yeah like we said like ones that are going to give me them in your life.
You could just click the next one please well thank you.
Okay okay so yeah so we'll just think of three things that we were really hope
that we will have achieved.
But yeah just have a little think about that one for a moment please girls and
write it down.
And it might be like I'm just going to add it might be something you've already
wrote for the last one like something you wanted to do this year and that's
absolutely fine.
And but yeah just wanted to add that.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
Okay we'll give it another couple of minutes and then we'll move on to the next
bit.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
Okay if you could just hit the next slide please well.
Thank you.
Okay so now that we've decided what's truly important to us we can name free
habits that we can create on a daily or weekly basis that will help us achieve
those things so just one habit for each thing.
So now we can start prioritising what's important and what's important to us
and good for ourselves.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
Okay we'll have one more minute just to finish this off and then we'll share if
anyone would like to share.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
Okay would anybody like to share some of their things that they hope they will
have achieved in this life?
[BLANK_AUDIO]
Okay I'll share one of mine and one of mine was to live in the moment more feel
like I've had like tunnel vision this past year just with one main goal in mind
and I've just been focusing so much on it and not probably probably not living
in the moment so much because I'm just constantly thinking about something else
.
So yeah so that's one thing that I'd really like to make a change on this year
and I feel like also a reason for that is being distracted as well with like
technology.
So something that I'm going to do every day and is just have less technology
and also just practice just being in this moment and not.
I think it's good to obviously make plans for the future and sickle for the
future of course but also this is the only moment that matters is the moment
that we're in right now you know what I mean because we're never getting this
moment back.
So yeah so I feel like I just need to bring myself back to the present moment
more and yeah not let myself get too caught up in thinking about the future.
So yeah so that's one of my ones.
Would anybody like to share I know these are quite personal actually so people
don't want to that's fine.
But if you do would love to hear.
So my three things that I would like to have achieved were to make the world a
better place to have been a great mum and to have enjoyed life.
Bully and Ben joyful and present so I'm going to you like being present is
really important to me.
I actually didn't think about the task you know the habits until after but
actually I think I think I do practice that pretty well I think I do my habits
are in alignment with like who I want to be and what I want to do.
The only thing I said was to like continue to like checking with myself and
encourage and support the kids because that can be hard when you're like and
working and like juggling a load of things.
So yeah to continue to and also it's quite hard like with things that come up
for you like that you might not have had when you're a kid or like things that
you're not so keen on in the world like my son is getting to the age where is
quite influenced by like YouTube and stuff like that
and I have to stop myself from being like having the wrong reaction so I have
to be really gentle and check in so that was that was my habit to continue to
check in with myself about my my parenting and yeah but I feel like I'm doing
well with those things
Yeah definitely me too. Thank you for sharing but yeah I think you're doing
well with that too well for sure. Like I said I said that's a few years ago and
it still stands.
I feel like if I had children I would want you to mover them because you're
just like the perfect mover in my eyes. So yeah I'm sure you're doing amazing
with that thank you for sharing well.
Thank you but she was enough.
Yeah I'm not sure if I'm going to have any so don't worry.
I'll read Sam's house as well she read something in the chat and she wrote.
I will write one of mine here as if I read it out I'd probably cry.
I'd love to make a difference to others to help them with believing in
themselves and I'm sorry I'm getting distracted by the noise that they.
themselves and achieving the things that they have limited beliefs about.
Just like this community has done for me because my transformation has been
life changing.
If I can give that to others like you've all given to me then I'd be very happy
on my death threats also too cute honestly like makes me want to cry but.
As we wrote back to yeah like you really have made a difference to others and.
Yeah what you've what you've wrote there what you would like you've already are
doing on a daily basis honestly Sami like you are incredible and what you.
What you bring to this community on a daily basis.
We are so so grateful so so grateful for you and.
Yeah honestly I just would not be the same without yeah so please already know
that you're doing that.
So yeah yeah I feel like you've given back like tenfold so and even just to see
your transformation was like joy in itself so.
100% but yeah I'm sorry I have chickens and then just making so much noise so
like that was.
Sorry about that but him but yeah thank you Sami that's so beautiful.
Okay we'll move on then shall we girls to the final exercise.
So now we know exactly what we want we know what's good for our soul we know
what's you know what's you know the goals we want to achieve this year.
So now let's take a look at creating a plan of how to achieve those goals.
So we're going to do this by taking a look at the smart goals model.
So we're just going to do this for two or three of the goals or as many as you
can get through but then at the end when we finish you can go back and look at
your some of your important ones and set out a plan for them and like do this
exercise with your other goals.
But like I said we'll just do two or three today.
And so we're going to go look at the bigger ones so on the face exercise the
ones that you would have put a free next to or a two or even one of the death
bed ones as well you can use one of those ones.
And we're going to break them down and make sure that the smart goals.
So a smart goal is specific measurable achievable relevant and time bound.
So you could have a goal of for example I want to lose weight.
It's very vague because it's not really.
It's not specific doesn't tell you how much you want to lose and how much time
you know so we want to go back through our goals and just make sure that we
really just.
Yeah just like break it down and see exactly how we're going to achieve this
because once we set a plan in motion and have simple steps of how to get there.
It's just going to be so much easier to achieve rather than having this huge
goal and not knowing where to start and just being overwhelmed.
And if we set out a clear plan then it's going to be just yeah just easier to
follow.
Can you just press the thing one more time I'm not sure if there's anything
else on there.
Okay, setting a clear plan of action that you know you are able to follow will
make a huge difference to if and when you achieve your goals also basically
already sets up it.
Okay then so let's go back through and do this.
So the more detail and the more specific you are the better because, because
yeah like I said it's just makes it so much easier to follow.
We'll spend about 10 minutes on this girl so just take your time.
And if anyone has any questions please just ask.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
So I'll just read out what the smart girl actually stands for because I didn't
do it then.
So the S is for specific so what do you want to do.
The M is for measurable so how will you track your progress.
The A is for achievable so how will you do it what what plans you need to set
emotion what steps you need to take today to start this.
Relevant so is this relevant in your life right now and finally time bound so
when do you want to do it.
So you can set yourself a start and end time as well so a lot of people say oh
you know like for example by this year I want to have done this.
But then by the end of the year they get there and they've not even started it
because they just you know forgot about it and let it pass.
Whereas if you set yourself a start date you could say you know what I'm not
ready to start this year to have all things going on.
But in two months time I'm going to get started on that goal and then six
months after that it'll be done you know so you can give yourself like a time
frame.
So yeah I think that helps as well when you procrastinate in is to give
yourself a time of starting it you know.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
Okay girls just another minute or two and then we'll finish up.
Okay then girls we'll finish this off here now and if you didn't get to finish
for all your goals then you can always go back through after this and make sure
that all the goals are smart goals.
But I'm going to hand you over to Elle who's going to just finish off this call
and yes over to you dear.
Thank you and thank you so much for doing this call it's been so nice to just
sit together and find out some of our goals and and to hear from people as well
it's just so much better when you speak your goals out loud or when you're just
in a shared space and doing this as other people in it so thank you really
appreciate you.
A couple of things that we'd end on so I was thinking about what Rebecca said
earlier about and bake it till you make it which is great but also it's not
really baking it you know it's growth.
Part of growth is that we do things when we feel anxiety you know we do bigger
things than we think we can do in that moment.
So I think sometimes it's a good idea you've got some goals written down now,
but inevitably we're human we're infallible will come across setbacks.
So maybe with these goals that you've written down you've got some you know you
've thought about what's valuable in your life what you want to do how how to
make these smart goals you've got some really good stuff there.
So maybe for each one of those you could write a plan for setbacks. So are
there any setbacks that you can anticipate because life gets in the way or you
know you've been in that position before and this thing happened.
So how can you make a plan for that setback so how can you give yourself some
grace or you know stay focused, not have a fixed mindset to talk about fixed
versus growth mindset growth mindset means that it doesn't always feel good,
but we
try we refocus and continue to try. So if there's any like if there's any plan
that you can make for if you have a setback might be a good idea to write it
next to any of those goals and even just like a little phrase or something that
you can say to yourself, you know like
I haven't made this goal by this time, but this is how I'm going to refocus and
I'm going to continue or I tried it this way and it didn't work, you know a
fixed mindset would be well now it's finished I failed a growth mindset is I'm
going to find another way.
That door might be closed, but there'll be another one so yeah just thinking a
bit about setbacks and how we can plan for those, maybe just making note,
making note of that but something a little bit of extra to do after the call.
I thought it might be nice to finish off the call today to send us all to
whatever we're going to go on to do tonight or to bed, whatever, with some of
the feelings of the goals that we've made, you know, Sammy talks a lot about
manifestation and I do think it's amazing to welcome in the energies of what
you want to achieve
as if you've already achieved them, then you're aligning yourself with the
energy of the things you want. So for anyone that would like to, maybe shall we
do just like, you know, 30 seconds, one minute or so like little meditation.
I'll invite you to if you want to put your camera off if you feel a bit more
comfortable, you know, without, without your camera being on then that's fine,
we'll put your camera off.
And then I didn't plan this by the way it's off the cuff so it's going to be
perfectly imperfect.
We just get comfortable wherever you're sitting, get comfortable if you want to
lie down or just try and get into a comfortable sitting position.
And we're just going to let the body rest as much as we can. You might want to
like just have a little rigour and just settle wherever you're sitting.
Close your eyes gently if you feel comfortable to do so.
Once you're in a comfortable position to gently close your eyes, and we'll just
do a minute or so that's all we're going to do and then we'll come back and we
can finish the call for today.
So the first thing we're going to do just to get into our body a little bit so
we're getting out of our minds now and into our body.
So all you need to do is just take some deep breaths, we'll do it together and
each time you inhale I want you to feel your belly with air and each time you
exhale I want you to just relax your body a little bit more.
So if you can feel any areas of tension in the body, we're going to relax them
on that exhale so let's take a few of these nice big belly breaths.
So we're going to go in and out and relax your shoulders and your body on the
way out and again in and out.
I'm going to continue to do those big deep breaths, nothing else at this moment
just listen to my voice and breathe into your belly.
So you might notice that your mind wanders or there are other things happening
in your environment that try to get your attention but that's okay, we just
bring our attention back to the breath and back to the body.
So you can notice how it feels when your stomach fills with air.
You might notice how the air feels coming out of your nose and mouth when you
exhale.
You can notice any pressure points so if you're sat down or laying down just
think about how the earth is supporting you, whatever you're sitting or laying
on is supporting you in this moment.
And just acknowledge that there's nowhere else you need to be, nothing you need
to do in this moment, no expectations.
There's a lot of self permission to be present in this moment.
Now into this space that we've created.
I want you to imagine yourself this time next year.
You can either choose one of the goals that you've been thinking about today.
In general, and I want you to picture yourself, your ideal best self one year
from now.
So maybe just start with thinking about what you're wearing.
What is that person wearing one year from now once you've achieved some of
these goals that you've set today.
You can see jewelry, what's her hair looking like.
And perhaps you can imagine her facial expression and her posture.
What's the energy that she's giving off.
Have a little think about her day.
What does her average day look like now that she's worked so hard to achieve
these goals that she set last year.
Now I want you to really, as much as you can, check into this future version of
yourself and feel how she's feeling.
Maybe there's a sense of pride or a sense of relief that you've achieved some
of the things that you've set out to do.
Just give yourself a moment to really check in and breathe into those feelings.
And lastly, just, I'd like you to offer yourself some gratitude.
Just feel that sense of gratitude about what it is that you've achieved that
you turned up today, that you even came, that you've written things down, that
you're on this journey that you're feeling these feelings.
You're allowing yourself this moment of stillness.
Allow yourself a moment to feel that gratitude for yourself in this moment.
And when you're ready, you might want to take just a couple more deep breaths
back into your body again.
And when it feels right, you can gently open your eyes, maybe just have a look
at the room around you just to sense yourself back in the room.
It's nice.
Oh, well, I hope you enjoyed that ladies I thought it might be a nice way to
just finish the call today, you know, we so often, especially a goal setting
and stuff we're so focused and like laser focus and looking forward and
striving, but actually it's so important just to be here in this moment.
So, yeah, thank you, thank you all for participating and for coming today.
And I was saying to G that perhaps, you know, we do this as a yearly call every
January, but perhaps we might like to do this in the six months time and we can
check in with some of the goals that we've made together.
So let us know if you think that might be a good idea.
And, you know, you might not want to because it kind of puts you in a very
relaxed state of mind actually done something like that. But if you want to
share before we leave, if there's anything that anybody wants to share, you
want to welcome, welcome to
us, I'd just like to say thank you so much for that rail that was like, that
was so, so nice and so needed right now so thank you. And of course this little
cry baby just brings all my emotions to the surface so thank you so nice.
Thank you, thank you for doing this for us today.
I was gorgeous. You as well Jay, I needed that and I needed that little
meditation as well I'm very basically being from a brain is still like, but now
I'm just like, so relaxed.
Yeah, good. Thank you so much.
And, you know, you can do that anytime, you can do that anytime you can sit by
yourself somewhere quiet, you can do a bit of a body scan check into your body,
and then you can bring into your awareness, whatever it is that you want to
bring in, you can speak to parts of yourself, because you can feel for yourself
, you can just feel some gratitude for the day.
You know, whatever you want to do it's nice to have a little check in a bit.
Ladies, it was so nice to see you all.
And we've got, and our next call is it next week, the week after.
And we'll post that anyway and group after this.
Okay, let me just double check and I'll let you know, if you like these 18 like
that.
Okay, it's the 15th it's Monday the 15th at 9 15 pm.
And this one is their ethical seduction and sexuality on cam.
And the one that we had to reschedule from last month.
So yes, so that's not Monday common, but the Monday after at 9 15 pm.
So yeah, it'd be nice to see you girlies on there if you're free.
But yeah, thank you again for everyone 10 and up and sharing today.
And, but yeah, and thank you for that at the end as well.
Well, that was so nice.
But yeah, I wish you all a beautiful evening and we'll see you soon.
Bye bye.